# **JONAH** DEL ROSARIO



# PROFILE

♠

Santolan, Pasig City PH



0998-398-9264



delrosariojonahagliam@gmail.com

Personable and knowledgeable IT support technician with over 3 years of experience in small and large corporation. Eager to share technical know-how and provide service to customers with various hardware and software related issues.

### EDUCATION

## DIPLOMA IN INFORMATION TECHNOLIGY

Polytechnic University of the Philippines 2013 – 2016

#### SKILLS

**PROFFESSIONAL** 

HTML

CSS

**BOOTSTRAP** 

JAVASCRIPT

GIT, GIT HUB

WEB DESIGN

COMPUTER HARDWARDE & SOFTWARE

DATA COMMUNICATION & NETWORKING

CUSTOMER & TECHNICAL SUPPORT

**PHOTOSHOP** 

MICROSOFT OFFICE

#### EXPERIENCE

Technical Support

• Jul 2019 - Present

### Shilo Events and Technology Corporation

Unit 306 Universal Motors Corporation, Chino Roces, Makati City

- Monitor and analyze network traffic of every circuit of customer via MRTG(Multi Router Traffic Grapher).
- Deal and handle client complaints, provide appropriate solutions and alternatives within the time limit.
- Designed and implemented the network system of the company.

**OSP Staff** 

Apr 2019 – July 2019

## **KLASH Corporation**

12 Bulacan St. Bonifacio Village Pasong Tamo, Quzeon City

- Design engineering plans as well as providing a route analysis of underground & aerial fiber optic installations.
- Site survey for planning, costs and schedules related to the project.

**OSP Staff** 

Oct 2017 - Jul 2018

#### GNP 918 Installation Corp.

Tandang Sora, Quezon City

- Design engineering plans as well as providing a route analysis of underground & aerial fiber optic installations.
- Site survey for planning, costs and schedules related to the project.

# **JONAH** DEL ROSARIO

•

## TRAININGS

- WEB DEVELOPMENT
   Mindtech Training &
   Development Institute Inc.
   Jul 2018 Aug 2018
- CNNA BOOTCAMP TRAINING
  Converge Training and IT
  Services
  Jul 2017 Aug 2017

# INTERESTS

- Photography
- Swimming
- Riding
- Driving
- Calligraphy
- Writing
- Singing
- Researching
- Playing
- Travelling

# EXPERIENCE

IT Staff Intern

Mar 2015 – May 2015

#### PRULIFE U.K

105 Paseo de Roxas, Legazpi Village, Makati City

- Developed functions, scripts and reports that were instrumental to the success of development projects.
- Performed troubleshooting for Internet problem, computer software and hardware.

Technical Support Intern

Apr 2014 – May 2014

### Security and Exchange Commission

Securities And Exchange Commission, Edsa, Mandaluyong, Metro Manila

- Install and configure computer systems.
- Diagnose hardware and software faults.
- Solve technical problems either over the phone or in person.

# REFERENCES

#### Gladys Barayuga

HRAD Supervisor Shilo Events and Technology Corp. P: 0917-190-4063

# Noli Java

IT Supervisor Shilo Events and Technology Corp. P: 0917-190-4053

#### Mc Donald Cu

Technical Manager Shilo Events and Technology Corp. P: 0917-190-4055